Zhang Tianyou!
Tonight, I'm taking your miserable life!
Young Master.
The thing in this coffin won't come out, right?
The Yin energy is surging,
making the corpse restless.
This thing is incredibly dangerous.
Tianyou.
Listen.
Aren't the sounds from this coffin a bit too crisp?
Zhang Tianyou.
Instead of hugging your pillow in the middle of the night,
you're massaging a coffin lid here?
Shu, cover me!
Cousin, why are you here?
Ling Yu.
Today, I'll help your Sheng Family
clean house!
Cousin!
Get him!
Ling Yu...
you look so beautiful in the candlelight.
Go, go, go!
Hurry up! Stop looking!
It's a ghost!
Help!
Save me!
The Eldest Young Master is still there!
Go!
Save me!
Give me a hand!
Cousin!
Careful.
Fill up the hole!
Aren't your two men still inside?
Fill what up?
Didn't you see how terrifying that monster was?
I didn't even have time to use my talisman!
Stop playing saint at a time like this!
Fine! If you want to fill it, do it yourself.
I'm not doing something so heartless!
Hey!
Stop arguing, stop arguing!
You... figure it out yourself.
I'm going back to my room.
Second Young Master.
How was our acting just now?
Not bad.
Good thing I figured out early on
the secrets buried beneath the Sheng Family.
Tell me,
how did your Second Young Master do
in that little tomb scare performance?
Vocals, lines, movement, and expression were spot on!
That's our Second Young Master for you.
What's acting all about?
Pacing.
Nuance.
Since I coated his legs in Bone-Corroding Powder,
in less than three days,
his legs will be completely ruined.
There are 16 days left until The Four Great Families' fated deadline.
Zhang Tianyou.
Given your methods and your words,
you can't be just a common Rogue Earthworker.
Who exactly are you?
Who I am isn't important.
When the Sheng Family chose me as their son-in-law,
it was only because my birth chart showed a Pure Yin Birth Time.
My fate is tough enough.
You wanted me on the Sheng Family's journey to the Tide Tomb
to act as a shield against disasters.
But right now, the Sheng Family is a sinking ship.
If you want to survive,
help me stabilize the Sheng Family.
All I can do
is make sure that in the coming storm,
you don't end up drowning.
Chief Leng.
Long time no see.
What kind of wind
blew a big shot like the head of the Qi Family
into my humble little temple?
I'm here to make a deal with you, Chief Leng.
As long as you help me take out one person,
our Qi Family
is willing to give you a few more lucrative old pits.
What do you say?
Whose life is so valuable?
The Sheng Family's live-in son-in-law,
Zhang Tianyou.
Some blind fool...
...paid to put you to rest.
Who are you?
For your trouble.
Go sleep in the next room.
I need to inspect the goods.
Be careful.
Ready to die a happy man?
You have an extraordinary build.
You don't look like you'd die young.
The gleam in your eyes...
...shines brighter than the luminous pearls in a tomb.
No wonder people can't rest easy.
There's a scent on you.
It's quite peculiar.
You raid tombs often, don't you?
Don't worry.
After you're gone...
I'll still visit you often.
If you really wanted to kill me,
you wouldn't have tiptoed into my room.
You've got a sharp mind.
And you're not bad to look at, either.
It'd be a shame if you died.
Tell me. Who sent you?
The one who wants you dead didn't want to come personally,
so they sent me instead.
Who do you think it is?
Judging by your looks,
you're not from The Four Great Families.
Miss,
the corpse poison in you has built up for years.
It's already seeped into your bones.
You only have a few days left to live.
Why don't we make a deal?
What do you have to trade with me?
I can help you purge all the corpse poison in your body.
And I'll also give your brothers in the Sand-Turning Gang
a large piece of territory.
And your conditions?
Very simple.
I need you to help me find a tomb.
It holds the Qi Family's original talisman manuscript.
Before the next full moon,
I need The Four Great Families' talismans and seal eyes,
the four great magical artifacts.
It seems you
are more than just a simple live-in son-in-law.
The rumors about the impending doom of the four families,
I've already heard them.
After I help you gather the talismans and seal eyes?
Are you going to become the head of the four families?
After that,
I need to find a tomb that moves,
to settle a 20-year-old score.
As for the rest,
Chief Leng,
knowing too much
might get people coming after you, just like me.
Well, I'm coming after you right now.
Zhang Tianyou.
You're like a nesting doll.
Peel back one layer,
and there's another one inside.
Hey, no, stop peeling!
You're driving me crazy.
It's been a whole day and night.
Leng Feiyan hasn't sent any news yet.
Could she have failed?
Dealing with that piece of trash
shouldn't be hard for her, right?
Go to the Sheng Family and test the waters.
Me?
Won't that attract too much attention?
If you don't go, should I?
Tiankun, don't forget
who's going to be in charge of the Qi Family.
Are you disobeying me already?
Fine, I'll go.
Mother? What are you doing here?
Tiankun, I heard everything just now.
Though your brother's birth mother died early,
he's still the legitimate son of the Qi Family.
The situation is unusual right now.
You must endure it if you can.
Mm.
Boss, this is the place.
But this place is a bit sinister.
It's the ominous "White Tiger Holding a Corpse" grave.
Doesn't seem like it's for hiding treasure.
More like it's suppressing something.
It's interesting the Qi Family hid things in such a place.
Xiaomei, what about the thing I asked you to look into?
Boss, publicly, Zhang Tianyou is the Sheng Family's live-in son-in-law.
Aside from his unique birth chart,
said to block disasters and absorb evil,
his background is as clean as a blank slate.
The cleaner it is, the more suspicious.
Go send him a message.
Tell him the goods are verified.
Ask him to pick them up in person.
Yes, understood.
Your dragon dowsing rod points to this perilous tomb.
Zhang Tianyou.
You said the Qi Family hid the talisman book in a place like this.
Is it to ward off thieves or to brew poison?
Maybe it's both.
Deception masks the truth.
The most dangerous place often hides the most crucial key.
Alright.
I've brought you here.
Our deal is done.
It's time you paid my reward.
Of course.
But removing deep-rooted corpse poison
requires using golden needles on your acupoints
to channel Yang energy into your body.
The process, well, might be a bit awkward.
All of you, get out. Guard the cave entrance.
Don't let a single fly in.
Yes, understood.
Alright.
Zhang Tianyou, show me your true skills.
Don't just be all talk.
Why are you just standing there?
Come here!
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
The energy feels wrong.
Yin energy, death aura...
And a faint stirring of something alive.